[ED.
Next week we will be doing heavy 하겠습니다.
We will study a new video subject
Please watch next week!
That's awesome.
Shall we go in one more time?
Wow, marinade!
We were indoors now,
We were indoors, but we were sweating a lot.
It took a lot of energy,
I felt like we used more energy than I thought we would after the event,
It wasn't just the people in front of me,
I wanted to make sure that people could use the Smile Garden more extensively,
I will do my best to bring people's eyes to the back of the garden.
Yesterday I thought it might not be so hot since it was dark, but it was really hot.
But it was a lot of fun, and besides our own performance, we only enjoyed the second half of the performance by the Zenha group.
I was able to see only the second half of the performance by Zenhaigumi.
I was able to see a little bit of their performance, so I learned a lot from it.
It was amazing!
It was great to see the rehearsal.
I thought it was a big venue with a lot of energy.
I thought that if I told the audience that I was doing a comedy show
I thought if I said, "I'm doing a comedy show," people would come up to me and say, "Welcome!
I thought I'd say, "Welcome!
Welcome!
I was listening to Laughing on the train and practicing my aari.
I was practicing my stirring while crying on the train because I was imagining the stage
I was so nervous that I thought I was going to throw up when I was at the Doll Factory.
I was so nervous that I thought I was going to throw up at the Doll Factory.
I'll do my best to improve on what I thought was not so good in yesterday's Doll Factory and give a cool performance at the Smile Garden.
Thank you for watching!
Today is the last day of the show.
I hope to see a lot of Ruff Ruff fans the moment I take the stage.
I was so happy to see so many fans of Ruff Ruff waving to me
waved to us.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!A-ha-ha-ha!
I'm scared
A-ha-ha-ha
Shut up.
First prize for preparation
I feel like a...
Looks like a frog.
I can't take any pictures.
Harl, what are you doing?
I don't want to burn.
You'll burn. Right there.
I'm meeting everyone at the benefit, so I'm just making a final visual adjustment.
It's great. It's perfect.
She's cute.
All right, that's it. We're all set.
Thank you very much.
I hope you're all looking forward to meeting her.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good night. - Good night.
Blue santinji.
Baca celery for the barbecue kids.
BAKAKAN
please?
Seino
Baka celery
Inside Baka Celery is a series of accelerator calls
BAKAKARUN
Thank you very much.
Yes, exit, exit
Exit due to solo
I, yes
Yes, Mr. Pro, please
Mr. Pro, in the middle.Mr. Pro, in the middle.
Please.
One left.
I want to take a picture now.
I'll do my best to make it really big.
I'll do my best.
I'll try my best to be cute for my fans and for you.
It's so cute!
Oh, no.
No, no, no!
It's raining! It's raining!
That's real rain!
Twice as much rain as you think!
Oh, yeah!
Ehhhh!
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no!
They don't look like they're going to move at all, do they?
It's going to take about an hour.
It's not good.
I hope it clears up. Smile curtains.
I hope it clears up. I hope it'll clear up.
I hope it'll be sunny.
I hope it'll clear up. Smile curtains.
I wish it would be sunny.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Nothing funny.
Who are you a fan of?
Dance Idol fans.
Become a fan of Rough Rough Paws.
Please.
Ruff Ruff.
What are you doing?
Look who's over here.Look who's over here.
Is it there?
Is it there? This.
It's possible as long as they don't find out.
If they don't find out, it's okay.
I did my best.
You did your best.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Take care.
I love this part.
Take care and I'm icing you.
Thanks for your hard work, Mayra.
Thank you.
Did you drink?
I drank, I drank.
Get some rest.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm happy.
Thank you for your hard work
Are you coming to see us live?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
What do you mean?
Sakura-san is coming to stage smile.
Oh, she's really coming?
Oh, really?
I heard that Sakura-san is coming to the Smile Stage.
Please come, everyone!
Please make it in time!Please make it in time for sure!
Thank you! See you soon!
Thank you very much!
I missed my youth high school 4 or 5 years ago?
Has the sun come down since I was here 4 years ago?
Oh, there you are!
Good luck! Good luck!
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Well, it's our last day, or at least it's supposed to be.
I'm glad we made it to TIFF, as well as the one-man show.
Well, we've got a lot of things to think about.
We've got a lot of things on our minds.
We're going to be thinking about a lot of things and making some strategies.
But the most important thing is that you guys will be supported
So we're going to increase our fans one by one.
We are going to increase the number of fans one by one.
It's like a battle, but have fun.
Yes, sir.
We're going to make you laugh out loud with our comedy act.
Laugh out loud!
Really?
Yes, I know.
I slipped a little yesterday.
I heard it was unbelievable.
But it's easier for people to remember you if you do it as hard as you can.
Don't do it with that shrug.
It's better if you give it your all.
Whatever you do, do it with confidence.
Yes, sir.
But you'd better stop crying, then.
Wow! I'll do my best!
Well, good luck.
I'm looking forward to it.
Akumo, watch the engine.
Watch the engine.Watch the engine.
Engine?
Uh, watch the engine.
Let's go!
Makeup illustrations! Makeup illustrations! We can't have everyone!
Confidence!
Smile!
Gratitude!
We, Lallah!
Hoo!
Let's go for it!
Yeah! Fight!
One down~
Go for it!
Sports Smile Garden is my dream stage.
I auditioned last year to be able to debut at Smile Garden this year,
I made it to the final round, but I didn't make it just in time, because it's a very important stage,
I had practiced so hard for the "Handsome" show,
See you soon!
Rallah up!
Let's do our best!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thanks for your hard work!
10 billion points I'll give it to you.
Ten billion points. Ten billion points already.
As long as you're alive now, that's all that matters
Bound by the curse of man
How long are you going to stay down there?
Kageyama Denanned
I have to be able to sing
No one can beat my barrel
My dreams won't stop, my smile won't spread
Runaway
What is the title of the song that is definitely not suited for a summer festival?
My title, my title, my titleMy title My title My title
I have to be able to sing. The answer.
I have to be able to sing
ME
Please give me more and more time to think about it.
I love it! Asa no commuting Nash!
ahahahahahaha!
Oh no!
I hate you.
Definitely out.
Buy the best one you can afford.
A little less arm, a little more rain.
You've had a lot of momence today, haven't you?
It's gonna rain harder if I don't have my arms.
Out! Out!
I would never do that to my arms.
No, it's raining like a motherfucker.
We exchanged a thousand cuts 10 years ago.
What?
Oh, my God.
That's crazy.
Even if you have to lie.
Keep the crowd happy.
Even if it's a lie?
Don't lie to me!
I have to answer. I have to answer.
You lie to me, and I'll lie to you.
You'll have a girlfriend by the end of the day if you have three.
I just got it.
It's a cool life.
Let's make the next day easy.
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
And now to the festival stage...
Good morning!Good morning!
Good morning!
I had the best time.
No, maybe during the Rheindiebenger.
I've cried before.
You were awesome back there.
That was awesome. That was rough free time.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
But the rain and the heat made it hard during the show.
How was it? Hajime-san.
Camera or no camera...
The food was good.
I didn't expect it to be so exciting.
It was pouring.
I think you did a good job of keeping the tension up.
I think you did a great job, but we've only just started.
I feel like we're just getting started with the performance.
I'd like to see more of that from now on.
I'd like to make sure that their good qualities are conveyed to the audience.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
An example.
Do you mind if I say a word?
Well, I don't think it's right to say something so arrogant at the beginning and at the end.
I don't know.
Yes, please.
Please do.
Yes.
I hope you can do it. It's the last one.
I would like to inform you about the future proceedings of the festival stage.
I'm very sorry, but we will start with Mr. Ruff Ruff.
I am very sorry, but Nekopla has been canceled.
We are very sorry.I am very sorry.
So, I will make arrangements for your future transportation.
For me?
Rahu!
Good night, Mr. Ohkun.
After this, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy If you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy, if you are attacked by the enemy
Shippuden Episode 134
I have to answer, I have to answer, I have to answer
In this corner you peeked at me
It's fun!
Yes!
Did some of you go to see it at random?
Hayashi, Ken, Millie, hang in there!
I don't want you all to catch a cold, so get home early!
Don't catch a cold!
I surely don't.
You still have to watch. Don't go home.
I'll cheer up!
Yes, sir!
Come up with some interesting answers!
Yes!
Smile more!
Welcome! Would you like a draft beer?
Yes!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
♪ Doraemon
# Leminade, leminade, leminade, I'll take it back
I got nothing
♪ Ten billion points, I said it again
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!
That's who saw it.Someone like that took a look at it.
Thank you.
It was amazing.
I couldn't think of anything else to say.
There were probably more people there who didn't know about Rough Rough than on any other stage,
At first, people who were looking at us like we were cartoon kings or just normal people waved to us at the end of the show,
It was a lot of fun.
But it was so hot that I was already stretched out after the stage was over.
It was fun.
It was so much fun.
That was amazing.
This was the end.
I couldn't get any more.
Also, the T-shirts were so identical to everyone else's. I thought they were so easy to find.
I thought it was very easy to find. The same with the penlights.
The T-shirts are great.
Even if you are not a fan, you might want to get one if you see one.
Yes!
I'm also fluffy with parents and children.
Even people with nice skin were clapping their hands from the middle of the show.
It was a lot of fun.
But, if I had included all the aori in the performance,
I think the way of thinking about street performance has changed here too,
It changed my way of thinking.
Seriously, YouTube changed.
It really changed the way I feel about live performance.
The feeling of running through.
That's the feeling.
If I had been MCing, I would have gone straight to the show.
I would've gone like crazy.
I guess it was because I was doing it that they changed me.
This song was my favorite song that I wrote,
I would like to sing music.Thank you for watching to the end.
Have you subscribed to our channel?
Have you clicked the Good button?Are you pressing the good button?
Is he eating?
Is he/she sleeping?
Are there any holes in your socks?
Have you paid your bill?
Are you thinking about your hometown?
Are you happy now?
I'm happy!